We're going to look at it from several aspects and the first thing that I would want to speak to would be the owner of the business, the CEO and in my profession, and I work for a company that provides wellness programs.
We've been doing this for a number of years and have been quite successful at producing results.
And so the real key to it is you Mr. CEO, you Mr. owner of the business and why would that be.
Well if you are not healthy, can you have a healthy organization?
If you are not setting the example, if you are not being the leader then who's going to lead.
I've spoken with several different companies and I can remember one particular bank president in his senior vice president, we sat down together and we started to talk about the subject of, because he wanted a wellness program, that's why I was there.
And so we started talking about it and I said to him, well you know there are certain things that are required to have a really a healthy group of employees.
And I said well one of them would be exercise.
You are going to have to have someway of getting your employees involved with regular exercise.
Another one is drinking water, we're going to get into these in a little more detail.
Another one would be eating a proper diet.
And you know when we got to that, I said, you know it's not just eating the right foods but it's also eliminating some of the bad foods.
And I said, you know like ice cream, ice cream is great but if you eat ice cream all the time, it's got so much sugar in it it's really going have an effect, and the president said whoa, you can't go there, that's my favorite food.
And so then I said well, maybe soda would be something that you would start with as.
And he said whoa wait, the vice president said we can't go there because you know because he's addicted to soda.
And so the net after our presentation I called back and I wasn't getting any callbacks.
We want a wellness program but we really don't want to lead.
But when you think about that, is that going to get the job done for you.
So I speak to you Mr. CEO, Mr. corporate owner, Mr. corporate president, you that are trying to produce something positive in your company, you need to pay attention to your own health.
Think about it, if you have a heart attack, if you are hit with cancer, what is that going to do to your organization?